Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Your servant greets the Lord.
عبدك يسلم على الرب.
No need for formalities, Du Momo.
لا حاجة للشكليات، دو مومو.
I asked you to teach the gentlemen at the Male Virtue Academy.
لقد طلبت منك أن تقوم بتدريس السادة في أكاديمية الفضيلة الذكورية.
How has it been progressing lately?
كيف كان التقدم في الآونة الأخيرة؟
My Lord,
سيدي
I am ashamed to have failed your trust.
أشعر بالخجل لأنني خذلت ثقتك.
Enough, enough.
كفى، كفى.
Speak plainly.
تكلم بوضوح.
I am running the Male Virtue Academy by your order.
أنا أدير أكاديمية الفضيلة الذكورية بناءً على طلبك.
It was going smoothly.
كان الأمر يسير بسلاسة.
But that Young Master Xie
لكن ذلك الشاب السيد شيه
seems to be acting on the Princess Royal's hint.
يبدو أنه يتصرف بناءً على تلميح الأميرة الملكية.
He keeps breaking the academy's rules.
يستمر في انتهاك قواعد الأكاديمية.
He has thrown the Male Virtue Academy into chaos.
لقد أدخل أكاديمية الفضيلة الذكورية في حالة من الفوضى.
It's a complete mess.
إنها فوضى كاملة.
I personally think
انا شخصيا اعتقد
the Princess Royal's temperament needs more refining.
إن مزاج الأميرة الملكية يحتاج إلى مزيد من التحسين.
She idles all day, unlike the Second Princess, who is dignified and gracious.
إنها تقضي يومها كله في الخمول، على عكس الأميرة الثانية، التي كانت كريمة ومهذبة.
She truly has the bearing of a noble.
إنها حقا تحمل طابع النبيل.
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
Who gave you the right to speak so recklessly here?
من أعطاك الحق في التحدث بهذه الطريقة المتهورة هنا؟
About the two princesses...
عن الأميرتين...
Please forgive me, Lord.
أرجوك أن تغفر لي يا رب.
I was careless for a moment.
لقد كنت مهملاً للحظة.
Enough.
كافٍ.
Du Momo,
أنت مومو،
you've served in the palace for many years.
لقد خدمت في القصر لسنوات عديدة.
You know what should be done,
أنت تعرف ما يجب القيام به،
and what should be said.
وما ينبغي أن يقال.
I shouldn't have to teach you again.
لا ينبغي لي أن أعلمك مرة أخرى.
I will remember your teachings, Lord.
سأتذكر تعاليمك يا رب.
And serve the Princess Royal with all my heart.
وأخدم الأميرة الملكية بكل قلبي.
That's enough, you may leave now.
هذا يكفي، يمكنك المغادرة الآن.
Yes, yes, I take my leave.
نعم، نعم، سأغادر.
My Lord,
سيدي
please don't be angry.
من فضلك لا تغضب.
Anger harms your health.
الغضب يضر بصحتك
The Great Learning teaches
التعلم العظيم يعلم
to manifest bright virtue,
لإظهار الفضيلة المشرقة،
to love the people, and to reach perfection.
محبة الناس والوصول إلى الكمال.
Knowing when to stop brings stability.
معرفة متى تتوقف يجلب الاستقرار.
Stability leads to calmness.
الإستقرار يؤدي إلى الهدوء.
Eunuch Afu,
خصي الكبد،
how much longer must I read?
كم من الوقت يجب أن أقرأ؟
Princess,
أميرة،
the Lord has ordered you to finish these classics.
لقد أمرك الرب بإكمال هذه الكلاسيكيات.
It may take until nightfall.
ربما يستغرق الأمر حتى حلول الليل.
Can you tell me the real reason?
هل يمكنك أن تخبرني السبب الحقيقي؟
Why is the Empress punishing me like this?
لماذا تعاقبني الإمبراطورة بهذه الطريقة؟
Well...
حسنًا...
Eunuch,
خصي،
my throat is hoarse.
حنجرتي أجشّة.
Get some tea
احصل على بعض الشاي
to soothe my throat.
لتهدئة حلقي.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
This...
هذا...
Princess,
أميرة،
I think your palace nanny often worries about you.
أعتقد أن مربيتك في القصر تقلق عليك كثيرًا.
Du Momo!
أنت مومو!
Stop right there!
توقف هنا!
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
Why is it her again?
لماذا هي مرة أخرى؟
Last time she asked us for things,
في المرة الأخيرة طلبت منا أشياء،
I got punished by the steward.
لقد عوقبت من قبل المضيف.
Let's go, quickly.
دعنا نذهب بسرعة.
What are you whispering about?
ماذا تهمس به؟
Stop!
قف!
Du Momo!
أنت مومو!
What are you carrying?
ماذا تحمل؟
To answer you, Momo,
للإجابة عليك يا مومو،
this is a coral bracelet offered to the Princess.
هذا سوار مرجاني تم تقديمه للأميرة.
A bracelet?
سوار؟
This is nice.
هذا جميل.
Momo,
يكتب،
it's meant for the Princess.
إنه مخصص للأميرة.
The Princess is busy with her studies.
الأميرة مشغولة بدراستها.
She has no time for such things.
ليس لديها وقت لمثل هذه الأشياء.
And you servants
وأنتم أيها الخدم
must always remind her
يجب أن أذكرها دائمًا
not to be distracted by trifles.
لا تشتت انتباهك بالتفاهات.
More sweets again?
مزيد من الحلويات مرة أخرى؟
The Princess eats sweets every day.
الأميرة تأكل الحلويات كل يوم.
How can her teeth handle it?
كيف تستطيع أسنانها التعامل مع هذا؟
Hand it over.
سلمها.
I'll keep it for her.
سأحتفظ به لها.
You may leave.
يمكنك المغادرة.
Yes.
نعم.
Such a stingy bunch.
مثل هذه المجموعة البخيلة.
Once I help the Second Princess win the Lord's seat,
بمجرد أن أساعد الأميرة الثانية في الفوز بمقعد اللورد،
I'll be sure to teach you all a lesson.
سأحرص على تعليمكم جميعًا درسًا.
Xiao Tao
شياو تاو
Princess
أميرة
What's wrong, Princess?
ما الأمر يا أميرتي؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
I've been kneeling all morning.
لقد كنت راكعًا طوال الصباح.
How did you end up like this?
كيف انتهى بك الأمر هكذا؟
Slow down.
ابطئ.
It's all because of Du Momo.
كل هذا بفضل دو مومو.
She complains about me to the Queen Mother every day.
إنها تشتكي مني إلى الملكة الأم كل يوم.
Says I'm lazy and ignorant.
يقول أنني كسول وجاهل.
Made me study etiquette and virtue all morning.
جعلني أدرس الآداب والفضيلة طوال الصباح.
I only just got back from kneeling.
لقد عدت للتو من الركوع.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
Xiao Tao,
شياو تاو,
where's this year's Peach Blossom Crisp?
أين Peach Blossom Crisp لهذا العام؟
I want to eat it right now.
أريد أن آكله الآن.
Well...
حسنًا...
Forgive me, Princess.
سامحيني يا أميرتي.
It's all my fault.
إنه خطئي كله.
Du Momo said sweets are bad for your teeth.
قالت دو مومو أن الحلويات سيئة للأسنان.
So she took away all the Peach Blossom Crisp.
لذلك أخذت كل حلوى زهر الخوخ.
What?
ماذا؟
She also took your reddest coral bracelet.
لقد أخذت أيضًا سوار المرجان الأحمر الخاص بك.
Du Momo took that too.
دو مومو أخذ ذلك أيضًا.
What?
ماذا؟
That Du Momo...
أنك مومو...
Princess,
أميرة،
please slow down.
من فضلك أبطء السرعة.
She's favored by the Lord now.
لقد أصبحت مفضلة لدى الرب الآن.
If you complain about her again,
إذا اشتكيت منها مرة أخرى،
you'll be the one who suffers.
أنت ستكون الشخص الذي يعاني.
I am the Princess Royal, I won't stoop to her level.
أنا الأميرة الملكية، ولن أنزل إلى مستواها.
I won't bother with a mere servant.
لن أهتم بخادمة فحسب.
I need a way to keep Xiao Yuanyuan
أحتاج إلى طريقة للحفاظ على شياو يوان يوان
and get rid of Du Momo.
وتخلص من دو مومو.
Massage
تدليك
helps you relax.
يساعدك على الاسترخاء.
It aids rest.
يساعد على الراحة.
It's an important lesson in the Male Virtue Academy.
إنه درس مهم في أكاديمية الفضيلة الذكورية.
Everyone must study carefully today.
يجب على الجميع أن يدرسوا بعناية اليوم.
So you can serve the Princess Royal well in the future.
لكي تتمكن من خدمة الأميرة الملكية بشكل جيد في المستقبل.
Yes.
نعم.
First,
أولاً،
put your hands on their shoulders.
ضع يديك على أكتافهم.
Come on.
تعال.
Begin.
يبدأ.
Press.
يضعط.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Press gently.
اضغط بلطف.
You need to use some strength.
يجب عليك استخدام بعض القوة.
Why is no one in front of me?
لماذا لا يوجد أحد أمامي؟
Because I'm your massage partner.
لأنني شريكك في التدليك.
What?
ماذا؟
You hit me and still want a massage?
ضربتني ولا تزال تريد التدليك؟
Dream on.
إحلم.
No way.
مستحيل.
Young Master Xie,
السيد الشاب شيه،
the Princess Royal brought you here to serve her.
لقد جلبتك الأميرة الملكية إلى هنا لخدمتها.
You must always remember
يجب عليك أن تتذكر دائما
even your life belongs to the Princess Royal.
حتى حياتك تنتمي إلى الأميرة الملكية.
Enough.
كافٍ.
Stop with the nonsense.
اتوقف عن هذا الهراء.
Hurry up and massage me.
اسرعي ودلكي.
When I feel comfortable,
عندما أشعر بالراحة،
your test will be considered passed.
سيتم اعتبار اختبارك ناجحًا.
I'll massage the Princess Royal, not you.
أنا سأقوم بتدليك الأميرة الملكية، وليس أنت.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Young Master Xie,
السيد الشاب شيه،
Du Momo is right.
دو مومو على حق.
Now that we're in the palace,
الآن وقد أصبحنا في القصر،
we belong to the Princess Royal.
نحن ننتمي إلى الأميرة الملكية.
We must accept our fate.
يجب علينا أن نقبل مصيرنا.
If you keep resisting,
إذا واصلت المقاومة،
you only hurt yourself.
أنت تؤذي نفسك فقط.
In my homeland,
في وطني،
a true man stands tall and proud.
الرجل الحقيقي يقف طويل القامة وفخورًا.
A man can be killed, but not humiliated.
يمكن قتل الرجل، ولكن لا يمكن إذلاله.
Men must control their own destiny.
يجب على الرجال التحكم في مصيرهم.
I won't massage.
لن أقوم بالتدليك.
Massage me now!
دلكيني الآن!
No.
لا.
I didn't expect this.
لم أتوقع هذا.
Young Master Xie is the boldest among us.
السيد الشاب شيه هو الأكثر جرأة بيننا.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Young Master Xie is different from us.
السيد الشاب شيه يختلف عنا.
I admire him.
أنا معجب به.
That's what it means to be a man.
هذا ما يعنيه أن تكون رجلاً.
Are you going to massage or not?
هل ستقوم بالتدليك أم لا؟
Will you or won't you?
هل ستفعل ذلك أم لا؟
No.
لا.
Beat me to death.
ضربني حتى الموت.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Hit me.
ضربني.
Du Momo!
أنت مومو!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Greetings, Princess.
تحياتي لك يا أميرة.
I'm so angry!
أنا غاضبة جداً!
I'm furious!
أنا غاضب!
That Du Momo...
أنك مومو...
How dare she hit my man!
كيف تجرؤ على ضرب رجلي!
She's truly out of line.
إنها خارج الخط حقا.
The palace test is always the Culinary Offering.
اختبار القصر هو دائما العرض الطهوي.
It's so dull.
إنه ممل للغاية.
Princess,
أميرة،
Why not make the Culinary Offering Young Master Xie's test?
لماذا لا تقوم باختبار العرض الطهوي للسيد الشاب شيه؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
The Culinary Offering
العروض الطهوية
has always been strict.
لقد كانت صارمة دائمًا.
Xie Yuan just entered the palace.
لقد دخل شي يوان القصر للتو.
I don't think it's appropriate.
لا أعتقد أن هذا مناسب.
But I've already reported it to the Lord.
ولكنني أبلغت ذلك بالفعل إلى الرب.
The Lord wants to test my Male Virtue Academy's results.
يريد الرب أن يختبر نتائج أكاديمية الفضيلة الذكورية الخاصة بي.
Enough.
كافٍ.
I understand.
أفهم.
Let it be the Culinary Offering.
فليكن عرضًا للطهي.
Yes.
نعم.
Xiao Yuanyuan,
شياو يوان يوان,
you must prepare well.
يجب عليك الاستعداد جيدا.
If you fail the test,
إذا فشلت في الاختبار،
you'll be expelled from the palace.
سيتم طردك من القصر.
Yes, Princess.
نعم يا أميرة.
I will do my utmost.
سأبذل قصارى جهدي.